rankedftw.com 2015-06-27

# Privacy Policy - Ranked FTW

Here is information on what types of personal information collected when you use and visit Ranked FTW. 

## Log Files

As with most other websites Ranked FTW save log files of all visist. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout the site. 

## Cookies and Web Beacons

Ranked FTW uses cookies to store information about settings on the site, those do not contain any personal information. 

## For Advertisments

Ranked FTW also use third party advertisements (through Google AdSense) to support the site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited. 

Ranked FTW also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). 

The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history. DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. 

You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting <http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx>

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. 

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added. 

## For Statistics

This website uses Google Analytics to help analyze how users use the site. Google Analytics is a web analytics tool that helps website owners understand how visitors engage with their website. 

Like many services, Google Analytics uses first-party cookies to track visitor interactions as in this case, where they are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. 

Google Analytics collects information anonymously. It reports website trends without identifying individual visitors. You can opt out of Google Analytics without affecting how you visit our site – for more information on opting out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites you use, visit this [Google page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).
